marketingexperiments.com 2018-01-25

# Privacy | MECLABS

## Privacy Policy

MECLABS Institute and its family of brands, [MarketingSherpa](http://www.marketingsherpa.com/) and [MarketingExperiments](http://www.marketingexperiments.com/), are committed to respecting and protecting your right to privacy. We will not rent, sell or barter your email address or other personal information to anybody unless you grant permission for this information to be shared with a sponsor in exchange for sponsored content. Sponsored content may include but is not limited to file downloads, videos, and reports.

### Your Personal Information

We may occasionally collect and capture some personal information with your consent for internal lead nurturing, specifically your full name, email address and company. This information may be used by MECLABS Institute and its family of brands to send you information about our services and to direct future webinar and event communications. If the offer is sponsored, we may ask you to agree to let us share this information with the featured sponsor of the specific access, webinar or event for which you register. Any use of this information by the sponsor will be in accordance with the sponsor's own privacy policy, if applicable. This information will only be available to the sponsor of the offer for which you register and will not be shared with any past sponsors or sponsor speakers. Any other use of this information will be in accordance with MECLABS privacy policy. If you ever have a problem with our use of this information and/or want to change or unsubscribe, feel free to visit our [MarketingSherpa](http://my.marketingsherpa.com/account/) and [MarketingExperiments](http://www.marketingexperiments.com/account/) subscription preference centers, or contact Customer Service at [service@meclabs.com](mailto:service@meclabs.com).

### CAN-SPAM Compliance

We will never send you an email blast on behalf of a third party. Furthermore, we will only send you emails related to any specific newsletters or topics that you explicitly signed up for with us. As a newsletter subscriber, we may send you very occasional invitations to participate in research questionnaires and to review the resulting data, or exclusive promotions for our offers and events. However, you can use our preference centers to add your name to our suppression “Promo Do Not Email” list. This is separate from our editorial newsletter lists, so you can be signed up for our newsletters but stop all promotional sends.

### Questions? Concerns?

Feel free to send them over to our Customer Service Manager at [service@meclabs.com](mailto:service@meclabs.com).
